

About Me

I am a developer who specializes in React apps, I have been working on personal projects since 2022 hoping to join a company that allows me to grow as a software developer.



1-849-392-4920



jdd1993@hotmail.com



<u>JosueDeLosSantos</u>



in/josuedelossantos



C/6 #16, Ens. Altagracia, Herrera, Santo Domingo Oeste, DO

LANGUAGES

- Spanish
- English

EXPERTISE

- React
- TypeScript
- JavaScript
- Node-JS
- **%** CSS
- HTML
- Git

JOSUE DE LOS SANTOS

Software Developer

EXPERIENCE

JavaScript

2022- 2023

Worked on 14 JavaScript personal projects, among them: a Battleship game, a To-Do and a Weather app.

Node-JS and React

2023- Present

I have developed many React applications and several APIs with Node-JS. I am currently developing full-stack applications with Next-JS.

EDUCATION

Ministerio de educación superior ciencia y tecnología (MESCYT)

Advanced English 2015

Universidad Del Caribe

Bachelor of Computer Science 2018-2024

SKILLS SUMMARY

React	100%
JavaScript	99%
TypeScript	95%
Tailwind CSS	100%
CSS	100%
HTML	100%
Node-JS	95%
PostgreSQL	90%
MongoDB	90%
Git	85%